Guide to the Administrative Papers of Chancellor George Bugliarello RG.007
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series II: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical Files
    - Science Advice to Next President Symposium, 1988 January-February (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Science Envoys, 2009 September 17 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Science, Technology & Society – Ankara, Greece, 1995 August-October (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Science, Technology & Society, Curriculum Newsletter – Setephne H. Cutcliffe, Editor, 1986 April (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Science, Technology & Society Encyclopedia, 1992 January - 1993 June, Undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Scirius Topic Page, 2008 May-July (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - The Seattle Forum, 1998 February-August (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Pasquale M. Sforza, 2005 April-May (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Sigma Xi – American Scientist Editorials, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Sigma Xi – Annual Meeting, 1994 April 14-17 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Sigma Xi – Carnegie Commission, 1992 October - 1993 December (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Sigma Xi – Common Wealth Awards Committee, 2008 June 25 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Sigma Xi – Convocation, Initiation Dinner, 1970 May - 1973 June (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Sigma Xi – Ethics Committee, 2007 March-October (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Sigma Xi – Fifty Year Membership, 2008 June (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Sigma Xi – George Bugliarello Prize, 2005 October - 2010 September (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Sigma Xi - Japan, 1990 September-November (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Sigma Xi - Lecture – "Reflections on Machines, 1996 August 23 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Sigma Xi - Miscellaneous, 1987-1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Sigma Xi – Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Sigma Xi – Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Sigma Xi – President's Symposium, 2006 March-April (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Sigma Xi - Scholars Center, 1990 October - 1991 June (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Sigma Xi – Edward Silberman, 2001 January – 2004 February (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Sigma Xi Forum – "Global Change and the Human Prospect", November 16-18, 1991, 1991 November-December (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Sigma Xi Forum – "Vannevar Bush II: Science for the 21st Century", March 2-3, 1995, 1995 January-March (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Sigma Xi Forum – Wingspread Conference on Global Change, 1989 March - 1991 August (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Seth M. Glickenhaus, 2003 November, 2004 March (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Smart Cities - Notes, Undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Social Technological Opportunities proposal, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Essays on Socio-Technology – Introduction – Notes, 1972-1973, Undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Essays on Socio-Technology – Socio-Technological Systems – Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Essays on Socio-Technology - Technology & the Evolution of Society - Notes, 1962-1971 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Essays on Socio-Technology – The University –Notes, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - "Some Thoughts on Knowledge as the New Societal Leit Motiv" by George Bugliarello – Draft, 1999 March (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Paul & Daisy Soros Fellowships for New Americans, 1998 January - 2007 June (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Spanish articles, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Spectrum Information Technologies, 1995 January (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - State Department - Office of Science & Technology, 2005 February 15 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - State Education Department – New York, 1993 December - 1994 March (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Stationary – Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Paul Steck Dinner, 1993 March 3 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Strategic Plan, 1992, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Dr. Jon C. Strauss, 1994 June-September (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - SUNY Downstate, 2005 June (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Sustainability – Journal of Record, 2010 May-November (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Sustainability Sciences Journal, 2009 September - 2010 July (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Sustainability Sciences Journal, 2010 August-December (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Teagle Foundation Incorporated, 1994 February, 2004 June (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Technological Literacy - Second National Science, Technology, Society Conference, 1987 February 6-8 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - "Technology" by George Bugliarello – Enciclopedia Del Novecento Instituto Del Enciclopedia Italiana, 1982 March 15 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Technology in Society, 1993 August - 2003 February, Undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Technology in Society – "Science and Technology in China, India and the United States Assessments and Comparisons", 2007 March - 2008 June (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Technology in Society – Special Issue, 2008 July-December (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Technology in Society – Sustainability, 2003 March - 2005 January (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Technology in Society – Urban Security, 2003 October (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Technology in U.S. Universities, Undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Telecommunications – Presentation, Westchester, NY, 1996 March (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - "Telecommunications' Impact on Politics, Economics and National Sovereignty: A New Game" – Conference on Communications, Technology, and National Sovereignty in the Global Economy- Northwestern University, 1995 March-September (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - "Telecommunications, Telecommunities and National Sovereignty: A New Game", Undated (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Teledidactics - Turkey, 1995 August (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Tokyo Denki University, 1993 May - 1994 April (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Richard L. Tomasetti, 1995 February (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Gioacchino Lanza Tomasi, 1996 August - 2001 July (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Tomsk Polytechnic University, 1994 January, 1998 March-April (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - TNO – Netherlands Organization for Applied Scientific Research, 1993 April (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - John Trani, 1997 January-February (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Transportation Security Proposal, 2003 March (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Il Piccolo Trieste, 1989 January 31 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Trieste, Italy – Area Science Park, 2000 September - 2003 October (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Fondazione Internazionale Trieste Per Il Progresso E La Liberta Delle Scienze, 2008 May-July (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Trinity College, 1996 July - 1997 November (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Trinity College, 1998 May - 1999 May, Undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Trinity College – Honorary Degree, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Trivium & Quadrivium – Research, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - John W. Troxler –Notes, Undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Trustees – Polytechnic University, 1992 January-September (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Trustees – Polytechnic University, 1992 October - 1993 September (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Tuition Rates – Polytechnic University, 1992 March (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Lucio Ubertini, 2001 June, 2003 April (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Uniao Panamericana de Associacoes De Engenheiros, 2008 September - 2009 January (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - United Engineering Foundation, 2000 May-July (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - United Nations, 1995 November (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - United Nations Development Program, 2006 March-April (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization – Tony Marjoram, 2006 October - 2008 September (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - United States Congress – Office of Technology Assessment – Construction and Materials Research and Development for the Nation's Public Works, 1987 June (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - United States Department of State – "Building Infrastructure for Sustainable Cities" Conference, 2004 September (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - United States Science and Technology Cooperative Program – Pakistan, 2005 August (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - University Cabinet Meetings, 2008 September - 2009 June (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - University Club, 1995 January-February (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - University as Developer - Great Cities Institute Project at University of Illinois, Chicago, 2001 October - 2002 January (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - University of Illinois at Chicago, 2000 February 22 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - University of Miami, 2009 June - 2010 April (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - University of Minnesota, 2004 September-October (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - University of Minnesota, March 2005-2007 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - University of Minnesota – Department of Civil Engineering Centennial Celebration, October 30, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - University of Minnesota – Honorary Degree, 2005 April 11 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - University of Minnesota – Honorary Degree Program, 2005 May 6 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - University Leadership Team, 2009 October - 2010 September (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - University Leadership Team, 2010 January-September (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - University Press – Inauguration Greetings, Undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - University Programs Panel Report, Undated (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - "The University Role in Helping Society" - George Bugliarello, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - "The University & the Urban Challenge" – Henry G. Cisneros, 1995 January (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Urban Assembly Institute in Math and Science for Young Women, 2008 June 17-20 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Urban Initiative, 2009 February, September (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - "Urban Sustainability and emerging Critical Challenges Beyond Water, Energy and Infrastructure, 2010 March-July (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Gianna Venturini, 1999 June, 2002 November (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - "Water & Society," by George Bugliarello, Undated (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Waterfront, 1996 May-June (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Dr. Ernst Weber, 1991 December - 1995 February, 2003 February (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Eli Weinberg, 2009 May (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Westchester / Long Island Advisory Board Members, 1994 November, 1996 July (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Whitaker Foundation, 1992 October - 1999 December (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - "Why Study Science and Engineering at a Private College," by George Bugliarello, 1994 April (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Dr. Patrick Wilson, 2001 April-June (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - World Bank - Overheads, 1994 December 5 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - World Federation of Engineering Organizations, 2004 May (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - World Future Society, 1995 January - 1999 June (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - World Health Policy Forum, 2006 April 7 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - World Traffic Safety Symposium, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - "Some World Views of Technology," by George Bugliarello, 1974 December (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Wunsch Student Center, 1991 October - 1996 October (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - XTEND Communications Corp., 2006 July (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Xu Kuangdi – President, Chinese Academy of Engineering, 2006 August-October (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Mina W. Zion – Reference, 2008 November (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Subseries B: MetroTech Center
    - Presentation to Senator Williams Delegation, 2000 December (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Editorials by George Bugliarello, 1985 January – 1986 December (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 1984 January - 1987 July (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings - George Bugliarello, 1984 March - 1988 September (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 1983 March - 1988 June (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 1982 April-December, 1986 November-December, 1987 January-April, 1989 February-December, 1990 January-February (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Adaptive Complex Systems Seminar, 1988 March (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Academy of Science Overheads, 1989 October 10 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Engineering News-Record Insert, 1992 February 10 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Journal of Urban Technology mention, 2008 May (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - The MetroTech Example Presentation, Undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - MetroTech Trademark Ownership, 1994 January - 1995 January (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Selwyn Seymour – Correspondence, 2005 September (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Polaris, the Scientific and Technological Park of Sardinia, 2001 May-August (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - "George Bugliarello: MetroTech Was His Vision" – Polytechnic Reporter, 2006 October 23 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Funding, 1988 January - 1989 February (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous – Speech notes, 1987 September (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1987 July – 2005 December (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 June – 2000 Spring (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - S.I.A.C. – Program, Undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Westinghouse Site – Residence Hall and Athletic Facility, 1992 February - 1997 May (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Promotional Material, Undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Transparencies, Undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Questions and Answers, 1984 December - 1988 October (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Presentations & Transparencies, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1992 November - 1998 November (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Map, Undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, 1983-1992 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Slides, 1989-1997 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Plans, 1992 January-February (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Leo Molinaro, 1997 July - 1998 April (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Press Clippings, 1982 March - 2010 June (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Slideshow, Undated (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Association of University Related Research Parks, 1993 December, 1999 February - 2000 September (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Advertising, 1982 April - 1983 August (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 December - 1990 February (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Fact Sheets, Undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Press Clippings, 1983 June - 1999 October (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Howard Golden (Brooklyn Borough President), 1983-1995 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - David C. Chang (Polytechnic President), 2000 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Michigan Economic Development Corporation, 2000 May 4 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - University of Bridgeport, 2000 June - 2001 February (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania Delegation Visit, 2000 December 5 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Bruce Haxton, 1995 January - 2010 January (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Kyoto, Japan - Visitors, 1995 October (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Proposal for Grant – MetroTech Study, 1994 September (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Promotional Material, 1995 February - 1998 December, Undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Presentations, Undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - General, Undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Triangle Area Research Director's Club (TARDC), 2001 March 20 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1993 February - 2003 June (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Transparencies, Undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Photographs, Undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Transparencies, Undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Petra Todorovich – Case Study, 2004 March-April (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Color Transparencies, Undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 1982 April - 2000 March (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Leo A. Molinaro – Technopolis in Thrace, 2002 September-April (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1995 August - 1996 June (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Ira Harkavy, 1997 November - 1998 March (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - MetroTech Board, 1991 August - 1997 October (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - History - 1, 1988- 1994 May (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - History - 2, 1983 January -1997 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - History – 3, 1982 May - 1992 March (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Polytechnic University: An Overview – Presentation, 1992 May (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Carlo Lotti and Associates – Presentation – Rome, Italy, 1996 June-December (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - YMCA - Joint Venture, 1994 January (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Miquel Barcelo Visit, 2007 September (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - MetroTech Institute, 2006 August-September (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - "MetroTech Institute: An Interdisciplinary Institute to Address Critical Urban Problems", 2006 September 5 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Wainova: World Alliance for Innovation, 2008-2009 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - MetroTech BID Website Info, 2007 September (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - MetroTech Real Estate, 1997 March 22 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Series III: Publications and Manuscripts
  This series contains published and unpublished scholarly articles and manuscripts written and edited by George Bugliarello as well as his handwritten notes and research material he used for various publications. The publications and reports have been assigned a number based on a numbering system adopted by the Chancellor's office to keep track of publications. A list of these publications has been inserted in the front of Box 28 for reference.
  This series is arranged by document type. The publications and reports and newspaper articles are arranged according to the publication number assigned by the donor and are otherwise ordered chronologically.
  - Subseries A: Publications and Reports (#3-#326, M, N)
    - #3 - Bugliarello, G., "La Resistenza al Moto Accelerato di Sfere in Acqua" (The Resistance to Accelerated Motion of Spheres in Water), La Ricerca Scientifica, Vol. 26, No. 2, (Feb. 1956), pp. 437-461. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - #4 - Ippen, A.T., J.W. Daily and G. Bugliarello, "Pertinent Factors in Flow Research on Dilute Fiber Suspensions," Tappi, Vol. 40, No. 6, (June 1957), pp. 478-486. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - #6 - Daily, J.W. and G. Bugliarello, "The Effects of Fibers on Velocity Distribution, Turbulence and Flow Resistance of Dilute Suspensions," MIT Hydrodynamics Laboratory, Technical Report #30, (Oct. 1958). (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - #21 - Bugliarello, G., "Some Considerations on the Analysis and Design of Hydraulic Machinery for Non-Newtonian Fluids," Proceedings, 1963 Meeting of the International Association for Hydraulic Research, London, pp. 1-8. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - #22 - Bugliarello, G. and V.Bahvnagri, "The Role of Flood Plains in the Correlation Between Flood Prediction and Dam Design," Proceedings, 1963 Meeting of the International Association for Hydraulic Research, London, pp. 21-28 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - #23 - Bugliarello, G. and G.C.C. Hsiao, "Phase Separation in Suspensions Flowing Through Bifurcations: A Simplified Hemodynamic Model," Science, Vol.143, No. 3605, (Jan. 31, 1964), pp. 469-471. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - #24 - Bugliarello, G., "Flow of Clay-Water Suspensions," (Discussion) Journal of Hydraulics Division, ASCE, Vol.90, (HYI), (1964), pp. 67-69. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - #25 - Bugliarello, G., "Man-Machine Communication in Civil Engineering," (Discussion) Journal Structural Division, ASCE, 90, (STI), (1964), pp. 253-255. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - #26 - Bugliarello, G. and C. C. Hsiao, "The Mechanism of Phase Separation at Bifurcations," Proceedings of the Third European Conference on Microcirculation, (R.G. Harders, Ed.), (1965), pp. 363-367. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - #27 - Bugliarello, G. and E. D. Jackson, III, "Random Walk Study of Convective Diffusion," Proceedings of the ASCE, Engineering Mechanics Division. Vol. 90, No. EM4, (Aug. 1964), pp. 49-77., 1964 August (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - #28 - Bugliarello, G., C. Kapur and G.C.C. Hsiao, "The Profile Viscosity and Other Characteristics of Blood Flow in Non-uniform Shear Field," Transaction, 4th International Congress on Rheology, Vol. 4, (1965), pp. 351-370. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - #30 - Bugliarello, G., "Exploratory Studies on the Stochastic Simulation of Outfall Flows," Proceedings, 1965 Meeting of the International Association for Hydraulic Research, Leningrad, 1965. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - #31 - Bugliarello, G., "Hospitals," Carnegie Review, No. 5, (Summer, 1965) (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - #32 - Bugliarello, G., "Microcirculation Hemodynamics and Other Biological Flow Problems: A Progress Report," Biological Flows Symposium, ASME, pp. 192-208, April 1965., 1965 April (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - #33 - Bhavnagri, V. and G. Bugliarello, "Mathematical Representation of an Urban Flood Plain," Journal of the Hydraulics Division, Proceedings ASCE, No. HY2, (March 1965), pp. 149-173., 1965 March (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - #34 - Bugliarello, G., C. Behn, C.E. Carver, E.M. Krokosky, J.R. Ripken and R. Shiffman, "Non-Newtonian Flows--Their Value in Civil Engineering," Civil Engineering, August 1965., 1965 August (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - #35 - Brandt, A. and G. Bugliarello, "A Simplified Model of the Flow in the Plasmatic Gaps of the Smaller Circulatory Vessels," Proceedings, 18th Annual Conference on Engineering in Medicine and Biology, Philadelphia, Pa., (Nov. 1965), p. 159., 1965 November (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - #36 - Bugliarello, G., "An Engineering-Oriented View of Biological Flows in the Relation of Engineering Mechanics Research to the Practice of Civil Engineering," EMD Specialty Conference, Proceedings, ASCE, (Oct. 1966), pp. 263-281., 1966 October (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - #38 - Bhavnagri, V.S. and G. Bugliarello, "Flood Proofing in a Flood Plain: A Stochastic Model," Journal of the Hydraulics Division, Proceedings of the ASCE, Vol. 92, No. HY4, (July 1966) pp. 63-76., 1966 July (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - #39 - Brandt, A. and G. Bugliarello, "Concentration Redistribution Phenomena in the Shear Flow of Monolayers of Suspended Particles," Transactions of the Society of Rheology, Vol. 10, No. 1, (1966), pp. 2-29-251. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - #40 - Bugliarello, G., J.T. Gormley, W.A. McNally and J. Onstott, "HYDRO, A Computer Language for Water Resources Engineering," Civil Engineering, ASCE, (Nov. 1966), 1966 November (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - #43 - Bugliarello, G., "Programming Needs in the Water Resources Field and the Role of a Problem-Oriented Language," Proceedings, IBM Scientific Computation Symposium on Environmental Data, (Nov. 1966), pp. 165-184., 1966 November (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - #44 - Bugliarello, G. and E.D. Jackson, III, "Study of Convective Diffusion from Continuous Point Sources by a Random Walk Model," Proceedings, 5th U.S. National Congress of Applied Mechanics, ASME, New York, (1966), (Abstract), p. 738. (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - #46 - Quevedo, C. and G. Bugliarello, "Stochastic Simulation of the Diffusion of Jets," Proceedings, XII Congress of the International Association for Hydraulic Research, Fort Collins, Colorado, (1967), pps.146-155. (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - #48 - Bugliarello, G., "The Role and Development of Problem-Oriented Computer Languages in Water Resources Technology," Proceedings, International Conference on Water for Peace, Washington, D.C., Vol. 6, pp. 573-585., Undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - #49 - Bugliarello, G., "Developing Creativity in an Engineering Science Course--Socrates Revisited," Journal of Engineering Education, Vol. 59, (March 1969) pp. 877-880., 1969 March (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - #50 - Bugliarello, G. and J.F. Sevilla, "Aspectos de la Hidrodinamica de Suspensiones on Sistemas Microscopicos," Proceedings, II Congreso Latioamericano de Hidraulica, 1968. (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - #51 - Bugliarello, G. and J.W. Hoskins, "Stochastic Simulation of Convective Diffusion in the Axial Plasmatic Gaps of Capillaries," Proceedings, 19th Annual Conference of Engineering in Medicine and Biology, San Francisco, (Nov. 1966), p. 183., 1966 November (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - #52 - Bugliarello, G and G.C.C. Hsiao, "Numerical Simulation of Three- Dimensional Flow in the Axial Plasmatic Gaps of Capillaries," Proceedings, 7th International Conference on Medical and Biological Engineering, Stockholm, (Aug. 18, 1967), p. 376., 1967 August (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - #53 - Bugliarello, G. and J. T. Onstott, "A Progress Report on HYDRO," Proceedings of IBM Scientific Computing Symposium on Water and Air Resources Management, Yorktown Heights, New York, (October 23-25 1967), pps. 197-191., 1967 October (Box 28, Folder 30)